hard-reset.com 2018-12-18

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.  
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.  
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.  
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.  
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.  
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.  
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

Advertising and Analytics Services  
We engage third parties to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and to provide analytics services about the performance of those advertisements. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of our website www.hard-reset.com, such as your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, date and time of each visitor request, referring site, browser type, language preference, links clicked and conversion information. The information may be used by us and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our website and other websites and better understand your online activity. We may also work with third parties to serve ads to you.

We receive and store certain types of information about your use of the website when you use the Website. Our purpose is to allow the website to work correctly, to allow us to provide our services, to evaluate use of the Website, for marketing purposes.

We may collect technical information such as your IP address, the address of a referring website or application, the type of web browser or mobile device you use, your operating system, your Internet Service Provider.

 How Google uses information from sites like [www.hard-reset.com](http://www.hard-reset.com/) or apps that use their services

<https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>

If you are a visitor from the EU please read the following article.

Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation) GDPR (Text with EEA relevance)

<https://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/?uri=uriserv:OJ.L_.2016.119.01.0001.01.ENG>

By using this website you agree to the placement of cookies on your computer and/or mobile device(s) in accordance with the terms of this policy. If you do not wish to accept cookies from this website [www.hard-reset.com](http://www.hard-reset.com/) please either disable cookies or refrain from using this Website.
